SQL injection matters because applications often enforce identity, access, data handling,
business workflows, and service integrations.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Command injection matters because applications often enforce identity, access,
data handling, business workflows, and service integrations.
LDAP injection matters because applications often enforce identity, access, data handling,
business workflows, and service integrations.
NoSQL injection matters because applications often enforce identity, access,
data handling, business workflows, and service integrations.
Parameterized queries Input validation Output encoding Selected CIS Controls mappings for
this topic include Control 16 - Application Software Security;
16.2 - Establish secure coding practices; 16.13 - Conduct application penetration testing.